This is not a country.
It's a front for a bank.
The politicians who work particularly at the electoral level are hired because they are being paid.
They are hired to pretend to look like they are working for you when in actuality they work for the bank.
We have seen less and less of this pretense because the bank is about to go public.
Remember I said it.
The United States has an unbreakable bond with Israel.
Israel is a true friend. It is our greatest ally in the region.
The International Criminal Court singles out Israel, but not Iran.
It's great to be here at the annual conference in support of the U.S.-Israel relationship,
a relationship that of course is anchored in our shared values.
Always also made clear that we continue to support Israel's right to defend itself.